[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these vampire films was directed by horror supremo Wes Craven?", "correct_answer": "Vampire in Brooklyn", "incorrect_answers": ["Vampyros Lesbos", "Vampires Kiss", "Vampires vs. Zombies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Summer Solstice is the point on the celestial sphere where the sun is at its most northerly point.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Hunt for Red October Borodin is killed by a KGB agent on board disguised as a cooks assistant. What was the KGB/cooks assistants name?", "correct_answer": "Loginov", "incorrect_answers": ["Kamarov", "Kasparov", "Padorin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A starfish is a type of fish.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which great composer wrote Wellingtons Victory , which included cannons, drums, and a lot of  brass?", "correct_answer": "Beethoven", "incorrect_answers": ["Mendelssohn", "Schumann", "Schubert"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the director of the 1959 film Operation Petticoat?", "correct_answer": "Blake Edwards", "incorrect_answers": ["Frank Capra", "Mel Brooks", "Alfred Hitchcock"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1986 Razzie for Worst Movie went to this movie that lost over $21 million. It starred Tim Robbins, Lea Thompson, Ed Gale, Chip Zien, and Miguel Sandoval.", "correct_answer": "Howard the Duck", "incorrect_answers": ["About Last Night", "April Fools Day", "100 Ways to Murder Your Wife"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does amathophobia mean?", "correct_answer": "fear of dust", "incorrect_answers": ["fear of numbers", "fear of rooms", "fear of candles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal does the greater siren, a nocturnal amphibian, resemble externally?", "correct_answer": "An eel", "incorrect_answers": ["A lizard", "A gecko", "A frog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Abrupt cessation of coffee consumption can cause caffeine-withdrawal headaches.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which part of the world is commonly described as Far East?", "correct_answer": "East and Southeast Asia", "incorrect_answers": ["All Asia", "Oceania", "East Siberia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do Robin of Loxley and Maid Marian get married at the end of Robin Hood: Men in Tights?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}]